So I'm not exaggerating when I say we are literally in the Anne Frank hiding families part
of history. My wonderful, beautiful, amazing friend, Lauren, is going to be spending time
in Minnesota to be helping with some families that are in hiding because their lives. I don't
think people understand the gravity of what our administration is willing to do to people
who are here legally on humanitarian visas and refugee status. There are so many children
who cannot go outside, whose families are literally stuck in hiding, and my wonderful,
beautiful, amazing friend, Lauren, is going to take activity kits for these kids, and she's asking
for help getting some. I'm going to try to put together as many kits as I can to give to
her. If you Venmo me, I can put together kits. If you want to put together your own kits and
I know you and or Lauren knows you, you can put kits together and DM me so we can arrange
in exchange. But if I don't know you and you DM me, I might, if I can't easily suss you
out, I, for the safety of, you know what I mean. As a mom of two toddlers, one day stuck
inside is brutal. I cannot imagine not knowing when the end is in sight for this. So let's
try to bring these kids as much joy as we can and their parents some relief. And then if
I'm sent more money than I can do with on the kits, I'm going to be donating it to bail
funds for the Midwest Immigration Bond Fund and Memphis bail funds. So I just want to get
that out there.